freeblogfactory.com 2013-05-01

# Privacy Policy - Free WordPress Blog Setup - Free Blog Factory

This Privacy Policy describes how we handle your personal information for our services on our www.FreeBlogFactory.com Web site (this “Site”). Our company, Social Spin, collects information from all end users of our services (the “Products” and/or “Services”), those who access some of our Services but do not have accounts (“Visitors”), as well as those who may purchase Products and/or Services (“Members”). We request that you read this Privacy Policy carefully.

## Personal Information Our Company Collects and How It Is Used

Introduction: Our company collects information in different ways from Visitors and Members who access the various parts of our Services and the network of Web sites accessible through our Services.

Registration: Members may be asked to provide certain personal information when they sign up for our Products or Services, including name, address, telephone number, billing information (such as a credit card number), and the type of personal computer being used to access the Services. The personal information collected from Members during the registration process is used to manage each Member’s account (such as for billing purposes). However, we may disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to potential partners, our affiliates, and reputable third parties. We take all available measures to select affiliates and service providers that are ethical and provide similar privacy protection to their customers and the community. We do not make any representations about the practices and policies about these companies.

In instances where our company and a partner jointly promote our Services, we may provide the partner certain personal information, such as the name and phone number of persons who subscribe to the Services as a result of the joint promotion, for the purpose of offering you other products and services.

In this instance, personal information may not be used by the partner for any other purpose. We may also generate non-identifying and aggregate profiles from personal information Members provide during registration (such as the total number, but not the names, of Members).

Also, with purchases, we supply our Member’s contact information to our business partners, who then may contact the Member by telephone after the Member’s purchase. Sales proceeds are collected by the business partner’s company.

## Consent to Recorded and Live Phone Calls

By clicking the accept button to this privacy policy, you hereby consent that we may place recorded and live phone calls to the number you provide. For more information contact info@freeblogfactory.com

Responses to E-mail Inquiries: When Visitors or Members send e-mail inquiries to our company, the return e-mail address is used to answer the e-mail inquiry we receive.

Special Cases: It is our company’s policy to use or share the personal information about Visitors or Members in ways described herein without additional notice or means to opt out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

Also, we may disclose personal information about Visitors or Members, or information regarding your use of the Services or Web sites accessible through our Services, for any reason if, in our sole discretion, we believe that it is reasonable to do so, including credit agencies, collection agencies, merchant database agencies, law enforcement, or to satisfy laws such as the Electronic Communications Privacy Act, the Child Online Privacy Act, regulations, or governmental or legal requests for such information; to disclose information that is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating our Acceptable Use Policy or Terms Of Service, or other user policies; to operate the Services properly; or to protect our company and our Members.

## Notice of Compliance to California Residents.

This Privacy Policy identifies the categories of personally identifiable information that our company collects through our Web site or online service about individual consumers who use or visit our company’s commercial Web site or online service and the categories of third-party persons or entities with whom our company may share that personally identifiable information.

Our company does not maintain a process for an individual consumer who uses or visits our commercial Web site or online service to review and request changes to any of his or her personally identifiable information that is collected through our Web site or online service.

See the section below entitled “Revisions To This Policy” for a description of the process by which our company notifies consumers who use or visit our commercial Web site or online service of material changes to our company’s Privacy Policy for this Web site or online service.

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is listed at the end of this Privacy Policy under the heading “Last updated.”

## For the purposes of this policy and California compliance, the following definitions apply:

Depending on the Visitor’s activity in our commercial Web site or online service, the following “personally identifiable information” may be collected in addition to information set forth in other sections of this document.

The term “personally identifiable information” means individually identifiable information about an individual consumer collected online by our company from an individual and maintained

## by our company in an accessible form, and may include any of the following:

(1) A first and last name.

(2) A home or other physical address, including street name and name of a city or town.

(3) An e-mail address.

(4) A telephone number.

(5) A Social Security number or EIN number.

(6) Any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of a specific individual.

(7) Information concerning a user that the Web site or online service collects online from the user and maintains in personally identifiable form in combination with an identifier described within this Privacy Policy.

Under California Law SB 27, California residents have the right to receive, once a year, information about third parties with whom we have shared information about you or your family for their marketing purposes during the previous calendar year, and a description of the categories of personal information shared. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to support@freeblogfactory.com and please include the phrase “California Privacy Request” in the subject line, the domain name of the Web site you are inquiring about, along with your name, address, and e-mail address. We will respond to you within thirty days of receiving such a request.

“Cookies” and How Our Company Uses Them. A “cookie” is a small data file that can be placed on your hard drive when you visit certain Web sites. Our company may use cookies to collect, store, and sometimes track information for purposes stated herein as well as for statistical purposes to improve the Products and Services we provide and to manage our telecommunications networks.

Advertisers and partners may also use their own cookies. We do not control use of these cookies and expressly disclaim responsibility for information collected through them.

Our Company Commitment to Children’s Privacy: Protecting children’s privacy is especially important to us. It is our policy to comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and all other applicable laws. Therefore, we restrict our Web site to persons eighteen years or older.

YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OR OLDER TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU ARE UNDER EIGHTEEN (18) YEARS OF AGE, YOU ARE NOT PERMITTED TO ACCESS THIS WEB SITE FOR ANY REASON. DUE TO THE AGE RESTRICTIONS FOR USE OF THIS WEB SITE, NO INFORMATION OBTAINED BY THIS WEB SITE FALLS WITHIN THE CHILDREN’S ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (“COPPA”) AND IS NOT MONITORED AS DOING SO.

Public Forums: Please remember that any information you may disclose in any Member Directory, or other public areas of our Web sites or the Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

Our Company’s Commitment to Data Security: Services and Web sites we sponsor have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. While we make every effort to ensure the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot guarantee that our security measures will prevent third-party “hackers” from illegally obtaining this information.

Where to Direct Questions About Our Privacy Policy: If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices described herein, you may contact us through the contact information provided on this Web site.

Revisions to this Policy: Our company reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy, our Terms Of Service agreement, and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner by updating this posting. Your use of this Site after such changes are implemented constitutes your acknowledgement and acceptance of these changes. Please consult this privacy statement pri or to every use for any changes.

Last modified: October 21st, 2010
